Chapter 3: To Strahl Again

Two weeks had passed since Rio and Aishia left the spirit folk village. Perhaps it was a result of Miharu’s prayers, but their journey was remarkably smooth. They arrived in the Strahl region unscathed, having not run into any dangerous encounters along the way.

Their current location was the eastern tip of the Kingdom of Beltrum, in a forest on Marquess Rodan’s territory. Rio and Aishia descended in a random area of forest when the sun began to set, setting up the rock house and settling down for the day. After that, they immediately prepared dinner and sat down facing each other at the table.

“We’ll arrive in the capital of Beltrant by tomorrow afternoon, so let’s go over our plans one more time,” Rio said to Aishia.

“Okay.”

“First thing tomorrow morning, we’ll head straight for the kingdom capital. Once we arrive, we’ll gather as much information as we can about the hero summoning while it’s still bright out. Then, at night, we’ll sneak into the academy and visit Professor Celia’s research laboratory. If her room hasn’t changed over the years, then we should be able to meet her there.”

“Got it,” Aishia acknowledged quietly.

“Professor Celia may know something about the heroes, so we’ll also ask her if she knows anything about Miharu’s friends, Sendo Takahisa and Sumeragi Satsuki. I may introduce you to her, too, but it depends on how complicated the discussion may get. Can I leave that decision until after we meet her?”

“Yeah. I’ll change into my spirit form and focus on guarding your surroundings,” Aishia said, volunteering herself as a lookout. Since she couldn’t be seen in her spirit form, being a lookout was the perfect role for her.

“Thanks, that’d be great. Now, since we’ll be getting up early tomorrow, let’s call it a night now. We were flying all day with only a few breaks, after all,” Rio said, smiling gently.

“Yeah, let’s get a lot of sleep,” Aishia nodded with a dazed expression. It seemed like she was sleepy already.

◇　◇　◇

The next afternoon, Rio and Aishia arrived at the capital of the Kingdom of Beltrum. They set up the rock house on the outskirts of the city as a landmark in advance and headed into the city.

At the moment, they were at the entrance of the main street leading to the business district inside the castle walls.

“Now, arriving at the capital is one thing, but...” Rio gazed at the street crowded with people and muttered to himself.

“What’s wrong?” Aishia tilted her face that was hidden by her hood and asked. Her appearance tended to attract attention, so Rio had ordered her to put a hood on. Rio, on the other hand, wasn’t wearing his hood.

“No, I was just thinking... It’s gotten a lot more lively here. It used to be pretty populated in the past, but... Let’s ask around in some stalls around here,” Rio answered with an unconvinced expression, suggesting they get a move on.

“Yeah,” Aishia nodded, reaching out to grab Rio’s left hand so that they wouldn’t be separated in the crowds. Rio gently held Aishia’s hand back.

The two of them stepped onto the crowded road, but it was difficult to make progress down the main street, so they decided to enter a random store and gather some information.

“There are no empty stalls around here. Let’s try going into an alley.” With a strained smile, Rio pulled Aishia by the hand and led her to a back alleyway.

“The alleys are crowded, too, but the stores at least have seats. Let’s enter one of them,” he said, wandering further into the alley. As he expected, there were more empty seats in the shops around there instead.

“We haven’t had lunch yet, so let’s get something to eat.”

“Okay... That one smells nice.” Aishia sniffed in the air and followed the scent before pointing out a shop. It appeared to be a stall selling sandwiches where a group of people were accepting their freshly made meals.

“Then let’s go with that,” Rio said, moving toward the stall.

He gave his order to a girl around twelve or thirteen years of age behind the counter. “Excuse me. I’d like to take two, please.”

“...” The girl took one glance at Rio and froze as though she was captivated by him.

“...Is something the matter?” Rio asked curiously.

“Oh, no, two orders it is. Please wait a moment. Mom, two please!” The girl shook her head with a faint blush on her cheeks before passing the order on to her mother behind the counter, where she was preparing the food.

“Yes sir, please wait a moment!” The girl’s mother gave a friendly nod and immediately began preparing the ingredients. She looked to be in her early thirties — still fairly young and with refined facial features.

...Hm? Rio looked at the woman’s face and felt a strange sensation similar to deja-vu, but he couldn’t think of a reason why, so he let it go and returned his thought process to his main objective.

“The main street is filled with crowds of people. Is it always that busy?” he asked the girl.

“Oh, I think some really high class nobles are getting married tomorrow, so lots of people are visiting from outside the capital. There’ll be some big celebrations and even a parade, or something. Because of that, even a stall located off the beaten path like us is getting customers, so we are very grateful,” she answered with a happy smile.

“Tomorrow... I see. May I ask which noble family...?” If it was a really high class noble, then there was a chance he knew of the family too.

“Umm, who was it again? Something like Ar... Ar...” The girl couldn’t quite recall the name, inclining her head as she searched through her memory.

“...The Duke Arbor family?”

The girl’s expression brightened as she nodded. “Ah, that’s it! It’s a noble by that name.”

“I see. That is indeed a high class family,” Rio said, recalling what he knew of the kingdom’s politics.

Holding the ceremony during a parade... Is it a show of power? The Second Princess’ kidnapping incident nine years ago should have caused Duke Arbor’s influence to decline greatly, at least up until I left the kingdom... Was there a shift in the political powers of the kingdom after I left? If I recall correctly... Professor Celia’s family was part of the Fontaine faction that was especially loyal to the king. Comparing the balance of the past with the present, he formed a hypothesis on what was happening.

“Umm, you really seem to know a lot about nobles, mister,” the girl said, looking up at Rio’s face hesitantly.

Rio’s eyes widened for a moment before he picked up on what the girl was implying and reassured her with an amused smile. “Hm? Yeah, but I’m not a noble, so you don’t have to be scared.”

“Ah, no! That’s not what I meant! I just thought you spoke really prettily, so I was wondering... It wasn’t that I thought you were one... Umm, you don’t have to talk to someone like me so politely. Ah, my name is Sophie, by the way!” The girl blushed, explaining herself with flustered gestures. On top of that, she introduced herself for some reason.

“What’s wrong, Sophie? Here, it’s done. Hand it to the customer.” The food had been completed and Sophie’s mother’s voice could be heard from the back.

“Ah, okay Mom. Here... Thank you for waiting, mister!” Sophie accepted the completed sandwich and offered it to Rio with a bow.

“I apologize for my daughter’s rudeness, sir.” Sophie’s mother also bowed her head deeply at Rio.

“No, you have a very cute and friendly daughter there. I enjoyed our conversation very much.” Rio shook his head with a smile.

Sophie’s mother sighed quietly in relief. “I’m glad to hear that, then.”

“If you don’t mind me asking, have you had this store here for a long time?” Rio suddenly asked.

“Yes, it’s been around five years now. I started when this child was still young,” the girl’s mother answered with a slightly curious look.

Ah, I see now. No wonder... A smile tugged at Rio’s lips as it all clicked in place.

“I see. I believe I may have visited this store once before, back then. No wonder I felt a strange sense of deja-vu when I saw the front of the store. I remember your daughter was tending to the store back then, too,” he said, explaining his sudden realization.

Sophie twitched in surprise at the mention of herself. “Oh my, is that so? Thank you very much for your continued patronage,” she thanked him happily, having no recollection of Rio.

The last time Rio had visited this store, he had been preparing for his journey to leave the kingdom after receiving his arrest warrants. Rio had grown a lot since then, with different colored hair to boot, so it was understandable that the mother and daughter wouldn’t recognize him.

“No, not at all. Here’s the money. Aishia, here.”

“Thank you,” Aishia nodded, accepting the sandwich and taking a small bite of it immediately. “...It’s delicious.”

“Please feel free to have a seat as you eat,” Sophie’s mother said with a pleased smile, stepping out from the back of the stall and setting up seats for Rio and Aishia beside the counter.

“Well, if you don’t mind.” Rio and Aishia both accepted the seats offered to them. Rio took a bite of the sandwich first.

“Wow, this is really good.”

The bread was a firm type of baguette and the fillings were a mix of meat and vegetables that were seasoned with meat juice and a salty sauce; it filled his mouth with rich flavor.

“Thank you very much. Please, take your time eating,” Sophie’s mother said, returning to the stall. Sophie occasionally shot glances over at Rio and Aishia. Eventually, Rio felt awkward enough to speak up.

“Umm, Sophie?” he asked.

“Y-Yes! How can I help you, mister?” Sophie replied happily.

“If I’m not disturbing your work, there’s one more thing I’d like to ask...”

“As long as no other customers are around, feel free!”

“Do you know anything about the hero that was summoned around four months ago?”

“Oh, there was a huge fuss about that for a while. A huge pillar of light shot up from the royal castle, so that kind of reaction makes sense!” Sophie said elatedly, recalling the events that occurred.

“The... has this kingdom officially announced the existence of the hero?”

“Yes — the castle issued a proclamation to the people.”

“Huh... Do you know the name of that hero, by any chance?” Rio asked with interest, but Sophie shook her head apologetically.

“I’m sorry, I don’t know the hero’s name...”

“I see... That’s all right. Thank you for telling me,” Rio said, resuming his meal. Aishia continued to chew on her sandwich in an adorable manner next to him.

“Thank you for the meal — it was truly delicious. I’ll drop by again if we’re ever nearby, so maybe we’ll meet again,” Rio said once they had finished their food several minutes later, leaving the store behind him.

“Yes, please come again anytime!” Sophie and her mother saw Rio and Aishia off cheerfully.

“What a lovely couple they were,” Sophie’s mother — a woman named Angela — said to her daughter.

“Yeah. I only saw a little bit of her face under the hood, but that lady was really beautiful...” Sophie agreed with a mix of fascination and jealousy.

“Fufu, it’d be nice if we could meet again,” Angela said, smiling amusedly.

◇　◇　◇

After lunchtime, Rio and Aishia continued to walk through the market in search of information. The sky gradually grew darker; eventually, all the stores closed up shop for the day. Instead, inns and bars started to bustle with life, but the two travelers had no business with those establishments.

Rio walked down the much less crowded main street beside Aishia. “All right, I guess we’ve gathered as much information from the market as we can for now. Sorry I had you accompany me for so long. Thank you, Aishia,” he said, offering words of appreciation to Aishia for keeping him company the entire time.

“I didn’t do anything. All the information was gathered by you, Haruto.” Aishia shook her head with a calm voice.

“No, having you beside me helped make people less wary when talking to me. You were a big help.”

“I’m glad to hear that, then.”

Though she had her face hidden by the hood the entire time, it was easy to tell Aishia was a woman from close up because of her figure. A man and woman walking together was easy to mistake for a couple, and a few of the store attendants were more willing to chat after being distracted by the glimpse of Aishia’s beauty that they caught. It was all thanks to Aishia that their bout of information gathering went so smoothly.

“I was thinking of going to the academy next, as planned. But if you’re tired, you can go and rest first...”

“It’s okay. I’ll go too. If we’re sneaking in, my spirit form might be useful,” Aishia offered without any sign of reluctance.

“...Then I’ll take your word for it and count on you. Let’s hurry, shall we?” Rio smiled with a mix of gratitude and guilt at Aishia’s devotion, before resuming their walk toward their objective. They were, of course, headed for the Royal Academy of Beltrum, where Rio once attended and Celia’s research lab was located below the library tower.

However, the academy grounds were deep inside the noble area surrounded by castle walls, adjacent to the castle itself, so there was no entering from the front. That inevitably meant they had to sneak in instead, but Rio and Aishia had access to spirit arts to make that task much easier.

The two of them went around the wall to locate a relatively unguarded location and leaped into the air with spirit arts, easily clearing the ten-meter-tall castle walls. They had waited until dark simply because it was easier to sneak around with the cover of night; there was no way they could have flown through the air so recklessly during the day.

“This way.” Rio jumped down to the roof of a moderately sized building and enhanced his body with spirit arts. Then, he burst into a light run across the rooftops of the noble district with Aishia bringing up the rear. With that pacing, they arrived at the academy in a matter of minutes.

As a former student, Rio made his way around the school grounds without hesitation. The number of guards were also fewer than the noble district, so they were able to reach the library tower with ease. Two guards stood at the entrance of the library tower, but with no sign of anything amiss, they didn’t seem very motivated about their jobs at all.

“There’s a terrace on the second floor at the back. The lock on the window there used to be easy to break, so let’s try that. If we can’t get it to open, you can enter in your spirit form and just unlock it.”

“Got it.” Rio and Aishia leaped up to the second floor terrace.

“I believe it was around here... Oh, it’d be faster to just get you to go inside in the first place, wouldn’t it?” Rio stood before the wooden window and looked at Aishia with a wry smile. She could also check if there was anyone inside.

“Yup, leave it to me,” Aishia nodded, dematerializing her form and disappearing from sight. Less than ten seconds later, a click sounded from inside as the window unlocked and creaked open.

“Come in. There’s no one inside.”

“...Thanks, Aishia. You made this so much easier than I was expecting,” Rio laughed, then climbed into the library tower and closed the window once more, locking it shut.

“Let’s go. Professor Celia’s lab is underground.”

They refocused themselves on the task at hand and headed downstairs. There were no guards inside the library tower, but there would be researchers working overnight — they couldn’t afford to let their guards down.

This sure brings back memories, Rio thought to himself as they walked down the familiar underground corridor. They advanced down the illuminated hallway, dimly lit by the light of magic artifacts, until they reached the room Celia used as her research laboratory. The name plate on the door was still carved with the name Celia Claire.

It’s still her name. Rio broke into a grin, then took a deep breath and quietly knocked. However, the inside of the room remained silent, with no sign of a reaction for several seconds.

“...Is she out?” He knocked once more to check before his expression fell with a frown.

“I’ll take a look,” Aishia said, turning into her spirit form. Her body scattered into particles of light and dispersed.

No such thing as privacy with her, huh? He hadn’t realized it before as she was usually in her physical form, but she could really abuse that ability if she wanted. Rio would have to have a talk with her about when and where it was appropriate to invade someone’s privacy — and who, of course, he thought with a wry smile. Soon after, the light particles gathered once more to form Aishia’s figure.

“Celia isn’t there. It’s completely deserted,” Aishia reported.

“You mean she’s gone home for the day?”

“No. At the very least, the room hasn’t been used at all recently. Most of the things in the room have been removed.”

Rio placed a hand against his mouth with a contemplative look. “...Looks like we’ll need to investigate this a little more,” he murmured in thought.

“What do we do?”

“It might be a little risky, but let’s see if there are any other researchers around and cast a spell on them. For now, let’s search as many of the research labs on this floor as we can,” Rio replied.

“Okay. I’ll search in my spirit form.”

Rio paused for a moment. “That’s probably the least risky option. Can I ask you to get to that right away?”

“Leave it to me.” Aishia immediately took on her spirit form and set about on her task. Then, less than a minute later, she materialized once more before Rio.

“This way, Haruto,” she said, leading Rio to the room she had marked.

“Thank you. What’s inside?”

“A middle-aged researcher. I’ll enter the room and cast an illusion on him before calling you, so come inside after that,” Aishia said. Illusion arts were a type of spirit arts that affected the five senses of perception of a person. For example, planting suggestions into someone’s mind was also considered a form of illusion arts. There were many different kinds of illusions, the most difficult and powerful of which were capable of making the other party experience what was, in short, a waking dream.

However, as illusion arts required time to cast, its effect was weakened when met with resistance — to the point where it could be completely repelled. In addition to requiring a great amount of skill in spirit arts to perform, it was also extremely difficult to use it in a practical way. Therefore, it was best to cast illusion arts when the other party was unaware of it.

Even if an illusion was forcibly cast, the illusion would be noticed the moment any resistance was met. Therefore, even if the art was successfully activated, the utility of the illusion was essentially ruined.

With all that in mind, Rio nodded uneasily. “...You’re right. It’d be better for you to cast the illusion arts in your spirit form, Aishia,” he said with a small sigh. “Remember, we’ve snuck into this academy in search of information about Professor Celia. We can’t have anyone realize that, so you need to put him into a dream state before he resists.”

If they could place him under a dream state before he noticed them, his memories of Rio and Aishia would be hazy even after the illusion wore off. Rio was capable of casting the illusion arts himself, but after considering the time lag between opening the door and approaching the researcher, he decided it was more reliable to have Aishia do it.

“It’ll be fine, don’t worry.” Aishia didn’t seem to have any concerns at all, as her response to him was blunt.

“...Yeah. If it’s you, then I don’t need to worry.” Rio gave a faint smile as he relaxed.

“Yup,” Aishia nodded, dispersing into particles of light again. Then, after a short while...

Come inside, Haruto, Aishia’s voice echoed in Rio’s head.

Rio immediately opened the door without knocking; a single middle-aged man sat at his desk in the room. Beside him stood Aishia, her hand held up against the man’s head.

“Hey.” The researcher seemed to perceive Rio’s entrance and called out to him in a friendly manner. However, his eyes were unfocused and had a dazed look about them.

He thinks you’re an important work-related visitor. If you want to ask him your questions, he should answer them properly — to the extent of his knowledge, at least. Aishia explained to Rio via telepathy. Rio gave her a brief thanks and began to question the man sitting before him.

“I have business with Professor Celia Claire. Where can I find her?” he asked.

“Shouldn’t she be in the castle?” the man replied casually.

“The castle... Why would she be there?”

“Hahaha. Duke Arbor’s faction may have regained their power, but the kingdom’s internal affairs are still very much unstable. They’re probably being wary of Duke Huguenot’s faction, what with the upcoming wedding ceremony and all.”

“...Wedding? Of who?” Rio almost doubted his hearing.

“Celia’s, of course. She’ll be wed to Sir Charles of Duke Arbor’s house,” the researcher stated the fact simply.

“Charles?! Charles Arbor and Professor Celia?” Rio’s jaw dropped, his shock making his words come out louder than intended.

His reaction made sense — Charles Arbor was the same person who forcefully tortured Rio under the name of interrogation during the incident where the Second Princess Flora was kidnapped. It went without saying that Rio didn’t have a very good impression of Charles.

“Well, it’s your standard political marriage. Celia’s family is from the Fontaine faction... Or rather, the faction recognized as the leading nobles with regard to their support of His Majesty. With the Huguenot faction chased out of the capital right now, they’re the perfect marriage candidate to increase the Arbor family’s power. And though it pains me to admit it, Celia’s worth as a genius researcher also gives her a high value as a wife,” the man explained.

“Professor Celia... No, the Count Claire family also wanted this political marriage?”

“That’s anyone’s guess... But with the current state of the kingdom, it wouldn’t be smart to turn down a request from the Arbor faction. It would have benefited Count Claire’s house more to side with the winners, so to speak.”

Rio took a deep breath and calmed himself down on the surface before continuing his line of questioning. “...I see. But I still don’t quite understand why she is living in the castle. What do you mean by being wary of Duke Huguenot’s faction?”

“The Huguenot faction is currently being treated as a rebel faction in this kingdom and have hidden themselves. But their power cannot be underestimated. A link between the Duke Arbor and Count Claire families would be most undesirable to them, so the families probably feared for Celia’s safety. It was for those reasons that she was taken to the castle.”

“I see, so that’s what happened... I suppose it would be easier to guard the castle...” Rio muttered with a grimace.

I guess a lot of political disputes occurred after I left the kingdom, huh? And because of that, Professor Celia ended up with the short end of the stick... He felt ashamed of his own ignorance of Celia’s predicament, though he couldn’t have known otherwise.

“...The wedding ceremony was to take place tomorrow, right?”

“Yes. There’ll be a grand parade and all,” the researcher confirmed with a nod.

Rio took another deep breath to calm himself down as much as he could. Then, he changed the subject. “On another note, could I ask you a few things about the dispute that happened with the Proxia Empire, in which the king and the Huguenot faction lost their power?” he asked.

There was no mistaking the fact that the shift in internal politics was what had prompted Celia’s marriage, but he needed to have a more accurate grasp of the situation.

“Mm... I’m not very interested in politics, so I’d just be repeating what I’ve heard from others.”

“That’s fine.”

“The dispute in question happened roughly half a year ago.” The Proxia Empire was a large military nation located to the north of Beltrum. The former mercenary and current first-generation emperor, Nidol Proxia, rose to power when he killed the king of a small kingdom forty years ago. He had since absorbed numerous small, northern countries and their armies, rapidly developing Proxia into the current empire. Because of their track record, the neighboring kingdoms became inevitably wary of the empire. Those sharing borders with Proxia — including Beltrum and Galarc — also had a history of getting into frequent skirmishes dating back to the first founding of the empire.

Despite this, ever since a military alliance of several kingdoms led by Beltrum and Galarc was formed to oppose Proxia, the tension between the alliance kingdoms and the empire had at least been reduced to a stalemate.

“The conservative approach His Majesty and Duke Huguenot had maintained for so long became their downfall as Proxia launched a daring invasion of one of our kingdom’s key locations. Our troops had their station captured and had to admit defeat.” The invasion had greatly changed the tension between Beltrum and Proxia.

“I don’t know the details of the retreat, but I heard the Proxia Empire’s strongest army, the Winged Knights, played a huge part in their victory. In any case, that was when Duke Arbor made his appearance. He hounded His Majesty and Duke Huguenot for responsibility over the seized location and had since taken over the role of negotiations with the Proxia Empire, which have been going fairly well.” As the researcher also doubled as a professor of the academy, his explanation was well arranged and easy to follow.

“After that, while I’m not sure of the particulars involved, it was thanks to Duke Arbor that our kingdom succeeded in making peace with Proxia. That Duke Arbor’s influence and esteem within our kingdom shot up, allowing him to turn most of the nobility in the royal court on his side and duly purge the Huguenot faction with just cause. He used that momentum to criticize His Majesty and seized a portion of his power.”

“Criticizing the king must have been quite a bold move to make...”

“That was how disadvantaged His Majesty’s position was. His Majesty has been stuck dealing with the faction rivalry ever since the former king passed away.” The researcher spoke of the issue objectively and sighed. He seemed to have the minimum amount of expected knowledge regarding noble society, but he truly didn’t seem to be interested in politics.

“On another note, do you know the name of the hero that was summoned recently?” He didn’t know when someone might visit this laboratory, so they couldn’t afford to chat for too long. Rio decided to quickly ask what he needed to know right then and there in a blunt manner.

“Ah, what was it again? I believe it was... Rui. Yes, it was Rui Shigekura.”

“Rui Shigekura, you say? Right, thank you very much.” While it was certainly a Japanese-sounding name, it was not the person Miharu and the others were searching for. After that, Rio confirmed a few more things with the man.

“That’s all. If you’d please excuse me,” he said.

“It was my pleasure.” The man shook his head amicably and saw Rio off. The illusion would wear off later, clearing his mind but leaving the impression that he had been napping.

“What will we do?” Aishia asked Rio after they left the room.

“...There are still some missing points in the timeline of the marriage, but there’s no time. I want to meet Professor Celia before the ceremony, so let’s sneak into the castle immediately.” It’d be easiest to hear the details of what happened from Celia’s own mouth.

“Then let me help, too. I’ll locate the room Celia’s staying in inside the castle.”

“Thanks. The castle is right next to this academy. If it’s just entering the grounds, then it shouldn’t be too hard, but...” The problem was locating exactly which room Celia was staying in. The inside of the castle was spacious and had many rooms, almost all of which Rio was unfamiliar with.

It doesn’t seem like there’s any kind of barrier set up around the perimeter, so the problem will be the interior... Especially inside the castle itself...

There was a technique using advanced wind spirit arts that could erase his figure from view, but it required moving at a walking pace to perform successfully. It also risked triggering any magic essence detectors and giving away their location, so he had to think carefully. They probably would have been able to break their way in and escape without an issue, but then the security would be tightened and make it harder to reach Celia.

“I’ll turn into my spirit form and search through the castle alone. That way, the risk of detection is lower,” Aishia uttered simply.

“...The inside of the castle will have zones with restricted entry, so they may have ways of detecting suspicious sources of essence. Ignoring the characteristic aura you emit as a physical spirit, won’t you be a mass of ode and mana in your spirit form? Are you sure?” They had considered this risk when they were sneaking into the academy too, but the royal castle was more likely to be guarded carefully in comparison.

“It’s no problem. If there’s any kind of barrier that detects magic essence, I’ll be able to detect it first. And the humans of the Strahl region typically can’t perceive essence, so my spirit aura shouldn’t be an issue, either. Plus, I don’t feel any spirits around here. As far as the radius of my detection reaches, anyway.”

“Dryas also said that wild spirits rarely ever appear in Strahl,” Rio noted.

“Most spirits are cowardly by nature, so they tend to avoid human habitats. The spirit folk who live together with spirits are actually an extreme exception, according to Dryas.”

“I see... Then can I rely on you once more, Aishia?” Rio requested reluctantly. He felt sorry for depending on Aishia so much, but they had to search as efficiently as possible right now.

“Yup,” Aishia agreed without missing a beat.

“Thank you. Let’s head to the castle right away, then.”

The two of them set off toward the castle.

Chapter 6: Against The Beltrum Royal Army

“I’ve decided,” Rio suddenly murmured to Charles below him.

“Huh?! D-Don’t tell me you plan on killing me?!” Charles’ body shook as he wailed in a high-pitched voice.

“No, you disgrace. I’m going to abduct this girl — she’s your bride to be, no?” Rio said, clearly provoking Charles, who turned bright red.

“Y-You! You think you can run away unscathed in this situation?!” he yelled in a rage. The carriage was already surrounded by the great army of the Kingdom of Beltrum; their numbers were easily in the hundreds. Once the reinforcements arrived, those numbers would multiply.

“Try and catch me, then. If you can, anyway,” Rio sneered, putting away his knife and lifting Celia, bridal style.

“Gah! Wait, huh...? Ah, u-umm... Sir Charles?!” Celia called in confusion, flushing scarlet when she was lifted.

“C-Celia?! Shit, you bastard!” Still being trampled on, Charles began to struggle in frustration.

“Celia?!” Celia’s father, Roland, yelled. He was being held back by soldiers, unable to bear the sight.

I-I’m sorry, Father. I will definitely come see you again... Celia’s face’s fell with sadness, but she mustered the best smile she could toward Roland.

“...What... Celia?!” All the strength drained from Roland, leaving him standing in a daze.

Here we go! Rio called out to Celia through telepathy, jumping down from the carriage.

“D-Don’t let him get away!” Charles yelled in a panic, scrambling to his feet. However, Rio had already landed on the ground with Celia and was running toward the soldiers with their lances braced.

“Don’t move!”

“What are you all standing around for?! Move!”

The commanding knight and Charles both yelled in tandem. While the soldiers were confused at the contradicting orders, most of them reacted to Charles’ order and moved in on Rio with their lances ready. However, Rio steadily accelerated toward the soldiers that had fallen out of step without an ounce of fear in his steps.

“?!” Afraid, the soldiers with their lances at the ready eased up on their approaching speed toward Rio. They suddenly pointed the tips of the spears toward the ground.

“N-No! He’s going to jump over the crowd of people! Brace your lances!” The commanding knight yelled, but it was too late. Rio had built up enough of a pace to leap before he stepped within range of the soldiers’ lances. He easily soared over their encirclement.

“...W-What are you doing?! Are you all incompetent?! Get him already!” Half-dumbfounded, Charles yelled at the circle of soldiers in a panic.

“Photon Projectilis!” The sorcerers who had been on standby in a corner of the circle started chanting their spells and fired their photon bullets at Rio above them. However, the bullets did not make contact.

“Fools, don’t shoot! What if you hit Celia?! Chase them! Capture them! Use griffins to chase them from the skies! Mobilize the Aerial Knights!” Charles raised hell as he sent out order after order.

Rio who had easily leaped two meters, landed gracefully outside the circle of soldiers. It was a jump distance easily two times as large as a knight that had enhanced his physical abilities with magic, leaving the soldiers in the circle stunned. Rio took that chance to start running again.

Caught off guard, the soldiers simply watched Rio’s retreating back. However, the Aerial Knights, who rode their griffins, responded immediately and began their pursuit.

“Listen up! The Aerial Knights have already began their pursuit. The entire army will now be mobilized to immediately encircle the capital. The transmission soldiers will first set up long-distance communication through magic artifacts and promptly spread the following information: the wanted is carrying a girl dressed in a wedding dress with a high chance he’s in possession of an ancient magic artifact with ability-enhancing sorcery. A regular soldier stands no chance against him. Only knights that can enhance their physical ability should attempt combat!” the commanding knight yelled loudly to the confused troops, making the flustered soldiers return to their senses with a gasp.

“Y-Yes sir, right away!” The transmission soldiers also began to move in a flurry.

“Those present should continue to guard this area. For now, Vanessa, you will be left in charge. Coordinate with the squad leaders and position them well,” the commanding knight said to Vanessa Emerle, the female knight beside him.

“Understood, brother!” Vanessa saluted him with a quick action.

Charles came over from the carriage and flared up at the knight in charge, Alfred Emerle. “Y-You! Alfred! What are you doing conveniently trying to give orders after you allowed the infiltrator to escape?!”

Alfred sighed quietly. “The one conveniently giving orders is you, no? Earlier, when I was sending orders to the soldiers under my command, did you not send your own orders and disrupt everything?” he objected.

“I-I don’t recall leaving you in charge of the security on scene in the first place!”

“Indeed, I believe that was you and your unconscious subordinate’s responsibility. With both of you unable to make the order, in terms of position, I judged myself most fit to take command.”

“Guh...” Charles must have realized he was at fault, as he fell speechless with a hateful expression.

Alfred ignored Charles’ blame shifting and moved the conversation on quickly. “Well, whatever. More importantly, did you gain any clues on the bandit’s motives? What is his goal?”

“...He said he had a vendetta against me,” Charles answered with a click of his tongue.

Alfred sighed quietly. “I see. Well, that leaves quite the number of suspects, then.”

“S-Silence! You should be pursuing the culprit, too! Go and seize him!” Charles yelled.

“That’s what I intend on doing. The prestige of this kingdom has been tainted as much, after all. Vanessa will be left in charge of this area, but I assume you will be able to take control of the overall situation from here, right?”

“Of course!”

“Then I’m leaving it to you. I’ll be going now.” With that, Alfred kicked off the ground and broke into a run. He hadn’t chanted a spell, but his speed was far above an average knight with enhanced physical abilities.

“Go already! Shit, shit, shit!” Charles shouted, stamping his feet on the ground without watching Alfred’s back. Because of this, he failed to notice the hero, Rui Shigekura, running behind Alfred secretly.

Meanwhile, in a corner of the garden among the gathering of attendees, the Proxia Empire ambassador Reiss watched the chaos on the temple grounds pleasantly.

While things have taken quite an interesting turn, this is quite vexing indeed. As an ambassador under their protection, it would not look good if I snuck away here. An assailant bold enough to attempt such a thing, and the spirit who never revealed itself... How interesting... Reiss sighed, lamenting the fact he could do nothing but watch in silence.

His interest was strongly piqued by the duo who had never revealed their identities — Rio and Aishia.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Rio was running over the rooftops in the noble district, heading toward the western side of the capital. As most of the nobility were attending Celia’s wedding, the only people remaining in the district were the servants in charge of watching the houses. The security knights and soldiers patrolling the ground would spot him at times, but were unable to catch up to him. Only the Aerial Knights riding on the griffins could keep Rio within their sights, and continued to give chase.

H-Hey, wait, Rio! This is so fast! Aren’t you going too fast?! Celia’s head was spinning.

Yes. Just make sure you hold on tight. The griffin squad in the air is a bit of a problem, so I’m going to increase my speed a little more, Rio said, increasing the strength with which he was holding onto Celia.

A-All right! Celia replied hesitantly.

His body was more muscular and sturdy than she had expected, revealing the growth that had happened in the time since they’d been separated.

You’ve grown into a wonderful young man, Rio, Celia couldn’t help but think out of happiness.

Thank you very much, Rio replied shyly.

...Eh, ah, did you hear that just now?! Startled, Celia blushed crimson red. She hadn’t expected her sudden thought to be conveyed, so she wondered if she had thought something rather embarrassing.

Ahaha, it’s because we’ve been in continuous contact for so long, it seems like our sensitivity to each other has temporarily strengthened. So even if you don’t think a thought clearly, it still gets conveyed.

Geez! Ah, hey... I wasn’t thinking anything else that was weird, was I?! Celia started to make excuses for herself in a flurry.

...No, there was nothing strange.

Hey, what was that pause just now?

Haha, it didn’t mean anything. Rio laughed in amusement.

Geez! Celia pouted her lips in embarrassment.

Have you gotten used to this speed a little? Rio asked out of concern for Celia.

Yeah, I’m fine. I’ve gotten used to it, so feel free to speed up all you want. Celia sensed that her earlier fluster had caused him to take more care and consideration around her, making her smile happily.

Then, don’t mind if I do. Rio raised his running speed by another level.

Just how fast can you run? Celia asked timidly.

If I really wanted to, I could go faster, but that would require a flat path. This speed is perfect for running across obstacle-ridden rooftops.

I see. I wonder what kind of sorcery it is...

That explanation can come later. Even if we run at this rate, it’ll take some time for us to lose them, so we’re going to descend to the alleyways for now. There, I’ll pass the baton and meet up with you later.

P-Pass the baton? Meet up later...? Rio’s sudden explanation left Celia tilting her head dubiously.

That’s the plan. There’s a place I prepared in advance with my accomplice... She’s actually the girl who spoke to you first, Profes... Oh, there it is. Rio suddenly jumped down from the rooftops. Celia curled up in preparation for the landing, but Rio used his wind spirit arts to land softly in the alleyway.

They were in an area for the upper middle class that served nobility, located relatively close to the castle walls that enclosed the noble district. The alleyway had been confirmed to be a dead end in advance, and with the closely packed buildings around it, it was difficult to spot from the skies.

“Aishia.” Rio hid in the shadow of the buildings and called out the name of his partner, who had remained in spirit form this entire time. The particles of light gathered to form the figure of a beautiful girl. At the sight of Aishia suddenly appearing, Celia’s eyes widened in shock.

“Wha?!”

“Aishia, take Professor Celia and get out of the capital, as planned. I’ll buy us some time.”

“Got it.” Aishia nodded once, taking Celia from Rio’s arms.

“E-Eh? Wait, what is the meaning of this?!” Celia protested from how she was being carried bridal style in Aishia’s arms.

“It’s exactly as I said. I’m going to become a decoy to buy us some time, so that you can escape the capital with Aishia. I’ll definitely meet up with you later, so don’t worry. As for an explanation about Aishia... Ask her yourself as you’re on the move. She’s trustworthy.”

“Eh, w-wait! It’s dangerous! You might be strong, but your opponent is an entire army...?!” Celia yelled in a panic to stop him.

“It’s fine. There’s plenty of ways it can be done in an urban area. Look after Celia for me, Aishia. I’d rather we concealed ourselves as much as possible, so if you fly in the air, make sure no one sees you,” Rio said lightly, before turning on his heel and walking away from the shadows.

“Yup, leave it to me.” Aishia nodded deeply.

Rio glanced back and gave a short nod. Then, he smiled gently once more to Celia, who was trying to say something, before jumping back onto the roof and running off.

◇　◇　◇

After handing Celia off to Aishia, Rio resumed running across the rooftops like an acrobat. The Aerial Knights patrolling the skies immediately spotted Rio’s figure.

“There he is! There’s no mistaking it!”

“But Lady Celia is nowhere to be seen!”

The captain of the Aerial Knights gazed down at the alleyway Rio came from and analyzed the situation immediately. “Hmph, he must have gotten desperate after being backed into a corner. The alleyway he came out of was a dead end... Tell the ground units to search the area, including the interior of the residences. Signal flare!”

Then, around half of the number of patrolling griffins circled back and released a powerful blast of light magic from the air.

“Signum Ignis!”

Rio gazed at the griffins in the sky above and focused himself with a deep breath. ...They called for reinforcements, huh? I’m not surprised. All that’s left is for me to distract my pursuers in a noisy way...

“Photon Projectilis!” The knights in the air all fired magic toward Rio on the rooftop in one go; a barrage of countless light bullets rained down on Rio. However, Rio moved about on nimble feet to evade the attack.

“I-I can’t hit him!”

“Damn it, how stubborn is he?!” The knights frowned with impatience.

“Keep your wits about you. He probably has an ancient magic artifact with a powerful ability enhancer. We simply have to nail him down to one spot. In that time, ground reinforcements should arrive. Continue attacking,” the captain in charge of commanding the squad instructed calmly.

“Photon Projectilis!”

Obeying their commander, the knights began to fire light bullets at Rio once more. Rio did exactly what his opponents wanted by lazily evading the attacks until the ground reinforcements could come running. About a minute later, the reinforcement knights — ten of them — arrived. The buildings were packed together tightly, but the roads were wide and allowed for a large view, helping the reinforcement knights immediately identify the alleyway Celia had been hidden in.

“There it is. Let’s go!” The knight who seemed to be the leader of the squad headed straight for the alleyway.

I won’t let you! Rio sensed the movements of the reinforcement squad and jumped down from the roof, blocking the way into the alley.

“Wha?!” The knights were taken aback Rio’s sudden appearance. Rio did not allow that moment of weakness to escape him, charging at the knights before they could draw their swords. Caught off guard, the leader took a palm thrust to the stomach before the rest of the tightly crowded knights came under a one-sided attack. Thus, six knights were rendered out of commission in an instant.

However, the next group of reinforcements could be seen approaching in the distance. I guess there really are a lot of them. Rio took out two daggers from his overcoat and stepped back for now. More photon bullets started raining down from the skies above.

“...Whoa.” Rio moved around in a zigzag pattern, evading the shower of bullets as he retreated to the alleyway, but the four ground knights took that chance to launch a counterattack on him.

In response, Rio stepped forward boldly and charged into the knights head-on. He swung the daggers in his hands to deflect the slashing attacks of the knights and twisted his body to land a roundhouse kick to one of them. He then widened their distance once again, using a hit and run tactic.

“Kuh! Don’t give him time to rest! Our reinforcements will be here soon! Tire him out as much as possible!” one of the remaining knights yelled, exchanging looks with the other two knights and splitting up to attack Rio from three sides at once.

“Yes, sir!”

It was a tactic that placed their willpower on the line. However, even Rio was standing there resolved to fulfill his role as the decoy. He had no intention of backing down. Swinging his daggers, he skillfully deflected the onslaught of attacks coming from the knights.

Unwavering before his disadvantage in numbers, Rio knocked his opponents out cold with his blows — first one person, then two, then three; every time they crossed weapons. However, the next knight squad arrived with no time for him to rest.

It might be a little tough... to get out of this one without causing casualties. Rio’s expression was grim. He hadn’t wanted to cause any casualties in this fight because of Celia, but it was difficult to hold back and fight against such an overwhelming number. If reinforcements continued to flow in like this, he may need to resort to using his spirit arts specialized for group combat.

But I’ve already made my declaration. I don’t want to do anything that’ll leave a foul taste in my mouth at the slightest.

Rio didn’t give up. He was the one who told Celia not to give up, after all. He had already decided to push his ideals through to the end, even if they were too perfect to be realistic.

“?!” Rio felt an unpleasant stinging presence from before him and suddenly stepped to the side. Immediately after he did, a flash; a light strike that would have knocked him out if it had made contact flew by, striking the ground behind Rio and cracking it.

That’s... Far in the distance was a towering steeple, and on top of it, Rio could see a boy with a bow held at the ready.

That boy was Rui Shigekura — the hero that the Kingdom of Beltrum had summoned.

Rui seemed surprised that his sudden shot hadn’t made contact, as he was standing there with his eyes widened in a slight daze.

It’ll be a pain if he continues to fire this way from that distance, Rio thought calmly. For a moment, he considered revealing his hand and firing a sniping shot back with spirit arts, but there was no need for him to resort to that.

“That’s enough. I will now proceed to apprehend you.” A single knight stood before Rio’s way. The knights immediately knew who the knight was, as a light sparkled in their eyes.

“S-Sir Alfred!” they called out.

...Alfred? That’s the name of the King’s Sword. He does seem strong indeed. Rio could immediately see that Alfred wasn’t your average fighter. In fact, whether he intended it or not, he had begun to release an awe-inspiring aura toward Rio.

“The number of casualties would only increase. All of you — step back and ask the Aerial Knights above to give the hero my gratitude for his cooperation,” Alfred said to the knights. He looked at the knights collapsed on the ground, before glancing up at the steeple in the distance where Rui Shigekura stood. Rui gave a strained but refreshed smile, shrugging his shoulders.

“Yes, sir. Understood!” The knights behind him nodded promptly, creating distance from Alfred.

“Hmph...” Alfred closed in on Rio in an instant. Then, drawing his sword in one smooth movement, he started with a lightning-fast attack.

A sharp metallic clash echoed; Rio had stopped Alfred’s sword with his dual daggers. The instantaneous offense and defense left the spectating knights gulping.

However, Rio and Alfred’s battle had only just begun.

The two first drew back their own specialized weapons, then the next moment swung them again, exchanging blows of offense and defense too fast for the eyes to follow.

“...?! There you go again, saying things like that...” Celia blushed bright red and buried her face in Rio’s chest once more. Then, after a moment, she started hitting his chest to shake off her embarrassment.

“It’s true. You’re just as youthful as you used to be, Professor... But you’ve become more beautiful.” Rio shook his head gently, speaking in a gentle tone.

“Ugh... I-If you want to put it that way, then you’ve gotten more handsome, too. You’re stronger, and taller, and more manly, and accepting of others, and... umm...” Celia started to say as she looked up at Rio, intending on getting revenge for his words. However, she gradually grew more embarrassed and ended up blushing once more, until she breathed a weak groan.

“Uugh...”

Burying her face in Rio’s chest once more, she clutched at his clothes. With how close she was clinging, she could clearly hear the thump, thump of Rio’s heartbeat. It was warm, reassuring, and very comfortable. Celia wanted to stay like that forever.

“Erm, thank you very much,” Rio said shyly. Then, after losing herself to Rio’s warmth, Celia returned to her senses with a gasp.

“Ah, yeah. I-I really am glad we were able to safely reunite. Well done coming back, and let’s leave it at that!” she said in a high pitched voice, her body shaking.

“Yes,” Rio said happily, giving a firm nod. However, his expression soon fell. “...I heard the news, Professor. You’re getting married.”

For an instant, Celia’s eyes wavered with sadness, before she soon crafted a fake smile with all her might and agreed. “Ah... yeah. That’s right.”

Seeing Celia like that made Rio take another step forward. “I heard your husband is to be Charles Arbor.”

“Y-You know about that, too?” Celia avoided Rio’s gaze timidly.

“...I apologize for being so blunt, but is this a marriage that you desired, Professor?” Rio got straight to the point with an utterly serious expression.

“Eh, no... Umm... Why so straightforward?” Celia gave a vague reply tinted with guilt and redirected a question back instead.

“I’m sorry, I know that I’m being awfully hasty. However, knowing that there isn’t much time until your wedding, and that Charles Arbor is the husband, I simply couldn’t wait around and do nothing. I didn’t get here through the official procedures, either.”

“...Huh? Umm, you couldn’t possibly have snuck in here, did you?” Celia asked in disbelief.

“I did.”

“This is currently the most heavily guarded area of the entire kingdom... If you really did sneak in, then that failure would reflect on all the knights and soldiers, and even the kingdom itself.”

“There wasn’t a problem with the security. I simply found a loophole catered to my abilities — it’s not like just anyone could have walked in, so you don’t need to worry about that. Both locating you and finding a way to sneak in took quite a bit of effort. However, since we’re low on time right now, I’d prefer it if you could just give a summary of what happened...” Rio said, returning the straying conversation back on topic.

“...Yeah, you’re right.” Celia nodded meekly. She must have still had her doubts, but she agreed with him nonetheless.

“Back when I was still a student, I remember you poured all your passions into your research and held a rather negative opinion toward marriage. Of course, it didn’t seem like you were completely uninterested...” Rio recalled, bringing up the past in question.

“...Is that so? That sure brings back memories.” Celia smiled somewhat sadly.

“That doesn’t mean you couldn’t have changed your mind, of course. Many years have passed since I last saw you, so its definitely possible for you to have had a change of heart in that time. That’s why I know it may be pushy of me, but I’d like to know if this wedding was something you wanted from the bottom of your heart, so that I can give you my blessings, too,” Rio explained honestly.

“Ahaha... I mean, I did agree to this wedding...” Celia gave a bitter laugh, but she chose to use the word “agreed” rather than “desired” — intentionally, perhaps.

“Even if your husband-to-be is Charles Arbor?” Rio asked, observing Celia’s face closely.

“...You have a connection to him too, huh.” Celia averted her gaze from Rio with guilt.

Rio formed a hypothesis with the information he had gathered earlier. “Was your house in an unfavorable position? And then Duke Arbor’s family came along, forcefully demanding the proposal?”

“...Mm, that’s... a rather unfairly subjective way of putting it. Because I am a noble myself, some ties to politics should be expected when it comes to my marriage. But I’m aware of all that, and I accept it. I’m already of the age, after all... I can’t keep thinking about my research forever.” Without showing any trace of her situation as a human sacrifice, Celia easily deflected the question in a light tone. To convince Rio further, she gave him a gentle smile.

“...So you’re not going to devote yourself to your research anymore?”

“Of course I’m going to keep at it. I’ll be quitting my position as a professor of the academy, but I’ve been allowed to continue my research at Sir Charles’ home. It’s a very favorable condition for me, don’t you think?” Celia said cheerfully.

“But are you really okay with that man?” Rio asked bitterly, his expression not completely satisfied with her answer. At that, Celia smiled faintly.

“You sure are bothered by that, aren’t you? To be honest... he isn’t my ideal husband. But I’m still a noblewoman — what’s best for me isn’t the only thing I can consider. I need to make a compromise somewhere,” she replied.

“Professor...”

“Besides, despite his demeanor, Sir Charles is a very kind gentleman toward the ladies, you know?” At those words, Rio felt an intense sense of opposition. However, Celia’s words of acceptance of Charles sounded convincing enough, which put a wedge between them; there was simply no room for Rio to insert his emotionally charged arguments.

Despite that, Rio refused to drop the subject. “That is... Is that really what you feel, Professor? I still can’t accept it.”

If Celia was truly fine with it and had really accepted it, then there would still remain a part of himself that stood in opposition. Was it because her husband was to be Charles Arbor? Rio wasn’t sure.

“...Then, will you have me instead, Rio?” Celia suddenly asked.

Taken aback by the question, Rio’s entire body flinched. “...?!”

“Will... Will you be the one to take me away somewhere and live with me for the rest of our lives instead?” Celia asked, her expression somehow fleeting.

“...If that’s what you truly desire, I will take you away from here, Professor,” Rio said, quiet but full of determination. At that, Celia’s eyes widened slightly.

“...I’m just kidding. Sorry, forget what I said. Just hearing that reply was enough for me.” Celia shook her head with tears in her eyes. Experiencing Rio’s sincere feelings like that made her feel very happy.

No. I must not drag Rio into this... Otherwise, he would...

Ironically, Rio’s words just now had solidified Celia’s resolve even further, which was why she stifled the bitter pain in her chest and pasted on a smile of happiness instead.

“Even if I threw away everything and left this kingdom right this minute, I wouldn’t be able to forget the family that I’d leave behind. Even if I went with you, I’d probably end up unmarried for the rest of my life...” she continued.

“Professor, I...”

“Listen, Rio. That’s enough. Go on your way, now.”

“But there’s still time...”

“No. I’m having a bath after this, so the helpers for that will be here soon.” Celia didn’t allow any form of rebuttal.

“I have to prepare for the ceremony early tomorrow, after all. They’d normally come a little later, but they could arrive any moment, now. If someone appeared, I wouldn’t be able to cover for you. The entire engagement could even be canceled if I was found alone in my room with a man other than my fiance.”

“...” Rio grit his teeth and clenched his fists in silence.

“It... may be difficult for us to meet again, but if you feel up to it, and if it’s possible... Never mind, I’m sorry. I’m glad I was able to see you before the ceremony. It’s embarrassing, so make sure you don’t come to the ceremony, okay?” Celia’s expression darkened faintly as she spoke, but she put on a cheeky grin at the very last line.

“...” Unable to find words that expressed his emotions, Rio remained frozen in place. Celia, in the meantime, pushed Rio around by the back.

“Go on, get going. Or I’ll yell... got it?” She pushed him into the room outside of the studio.

“I won’t ask how you got in, but you can’t be spotted on your way out, okay? Make sure you’re out of here within 20 seconds of me closing this door. If you’re still in the room, I really will scream, okay? Goodbye,” She said, closing the door without waiting for Rio’s reply. She felt as though she wouldn’t be able to catch her breath if she continued looking at Rio’s face any longer.

After that, Celia carefully counted down the 20 seconds before fearfully opening the door to the studio once more. There was no sign of anyone in the room.

“Has he left...? Wait. Zona Revelare.”

Just to be sure, Celia used an ability to detect any reactions to magic essence nearby. A magic circle appeared by her feet, sending a wave of essence to search for any other magic sources in her room and the surrounding area.

“There’s only the knights guarding the corridor... There’s no one outside the building.”

Celia suddenly looked toward the window connected to the terrace. Finding the lock on the inside left completely unlocked, she deduced that Rio had probably entered from there. She immediately locked it once more, letting the sound of the lock clicking shut echo uselessly in the room.

Tears started pouring from Celia’s eyes. “...Thank you, Rio. It really made me happy to see you one more time. So long...”

She offered words of gratitude and a farewell to someone that was no longer present.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, after Rio left Celia’s room, he immediately met up with Aishia in her physical form and flew up into the night sky together.

“Are you feeling conflicted, Haruto?” Aishia asked, seeing the sour expression on his face.

“No, I don’t think I’m conflicted... Maybe. It’s more like I haven’t fully accepted it yet.”

“Why?”

“...Because I couldn’t see what she was truly feeling,” Rio mumbled in reply.

“Then what do you want to do?” Aishia asked, inquiring about his true intentions.

“We’ll go watch the ceremony tomorrow. But first, I want to know more details about how the marriage between the Count Claire house and Duke Arbor’s house came to be.”

Because it didn’t seem like he’d be able to talk to Celia properly without knowing that.

“I’ll help,” Aishia offered without any hesitation.

“...Sorry.” Rio apologized shamefully.

“Why are you apologizing?”

“Because I’m making you go along with my every whim.”

“I told you before — Haruto and I will always be together. As long as you need me, I will always be here for you to lean on. So... lean on me,” Aishia said, hugging Rio gently midair.

“...Thanks. I don’t want to impede our information search by causing a fuss, so we’ll proceed carefully. It might be a bit of a long night, but will you come with me?”

“Leave it to me. Let’s go.” Aishia nodded, taking Rio by the hand.

Their night had only just begun.

“Tch, that fool, bringing shame to the family...” Duke Arbor came over too, twisting his face in annoyance at the disgraceful sight of his son.

“W-Wait, please! It’s too dangerous. Don’t provoke the bandit!” The soldiers hurried to halt Count Clare and Duke Arbor in their steps.

“Argh, release me! Didn’t you tell me your security measures were perfect?!” Roland wailed, breathing roughly. In the meantime, the black figure confirmed the situation around them through his hood.

Professor Celia — it’s me, Rio. I apologize for the fuss, but I wanted to take the chance to talk to you while our surroundings are doused in confusion. If you could remain silent for a moment, I would greatly appreciate it, he spoke to Celia through telepathic spirit arts.

“?!” Celia gasped and stiffened in the face. However, she seemed to have built some resistance to the shock of telepathy through her encounter with Aishia earlier, as she seemed to accept the situation without much of a reaction. She waited for Rio’s words with a worried look.

First of all, I am communicating to your mind through a method called telepathy. This cannot be used without direct contact with the other, so please remain restrained like this for a while. It’ll act as a control to our surroundings too. If you think your thoughts strongly and clearly, they’ll reach me too, so if you have any questions... Rio began to explain to Celia while being wary of their surroundings.

So it really was your doing, wasn’t it?! What is the meaning of this?! Celia questioned Rio without a moment’s hesitation. But before Rio could respond, Charles grew tired at their feet and started to make a fuss.

“Y-You! How long do you intend on using me as a footrest?! Who sent you? What do you want?!”

Rio sighed quietly. “Silence. I have a vendetta against you. I’m considering my options right now, and I don’t mind simply crushing your spine like this, honestly,” he said, putting more force into the foot on Charles.

W-Wait, Rio?!

Don’t worry — I won’t kill anyone. It’s an act to make a distraction, because he’s a bit nosy.

Y-Yeah... Celia nodded timidly at Rio’s explanation.

“Ngh...” Charles must have sensed how the weight on his back was threatening his life and immediately fell silent.

Meanwhile, the surroundings were in extreme chaos, with people trying to evacuate the attendees while also trying to surrounding the horse carriage. However, they appeared to fear for the safety of Celia and Charles who had been taken hostage, as they didn’t try any bold actions.

Rio decided to take that time to continue his explanation. There’s no time, so let me say this quickly: I want to hear what your true feelings are one more time, before you get married. That is why I have come, he said flatly.

Wh-What do you mean, “that is why”? What are you thinking, doing something like this?! You’ll be captured, you know!! Celia yelled in her head in a panic.

I said I wanted to hear what your true feelings are, Professor. Even so, Rio showed no sign of impatience as he spoke in a firm tone.

T-That’s... I told you, I... Pressured by Rio’s determination, Celia’s face fell with chagrin.

You can’t fool me. I came here knowing roughly the whole story behind this political marriage. About how the Count Claire house was placed under a certain suspicion, which the Duke Arbor house half threatened. I understand why you were put in this situation, Professor.

Huh?! W-Where did you hear that?! Celia gasped, her expression changing.

I crossed a dangerous bridge... But none of that matters right now. Rio dismissed her question curtly.

I-It should matter... There were many things she wanted to ask about in that short exchange just now, but Rio’s forceful attitude rendered Celia speechless.

...Won’t you tell me, please? Assuming there was no need for you to sacrifice yourself, would you still want to marry this man, Professor? That’s all I wanted to ask, Rio asked smoothly as he looked down at Charles below him, almost as though he could see right through Celia’s heart.

What will you do... after I answer? Celia asked in a weak and timid way.

If you so desire, I will bring this wedding to a halt. Just like how you readily accepted this political marriage, I readily accepted my choice to do that before coming here, Rio said with determination.

...You’re being too overbearing.

I am fully aware of how overbearing and forceful I’m being. I’ve already overstepped that line by interfering with your wedding in the first place, Professor.

If you understand that much, why... Why are you doing such a thing? Celia asked timidly.

Because I couldn’t accept it. You’re important to me, Professor — if I hadn’t come today, at this moment, I would have regretted it for the rest of my life. I don’t want to lose the people who are most important to me without doing anything about it... I’ve already lost important things to me and regretted it quite a bit. Once something is lost, you can never get it back, but... there’s still time before you lose it. Rio’s declaration was almost gallantly self-centered.

...! For some reason, Celia felt a certain weight to it; Rio’s words deeply resonated in her chest. I am unable to just sit back and watch as your dignity is trampled on for the rest of your life, Professor. Will you eventually become happy in this marriage? If you can tell me that you will, I will quietly leave this place. I’ll never appear before you again, Rio said simply.

If Celia had the resolution and confidence to assert that she would be happy, then Rio was just as ready and determined to back away. But if she faltered... Well, that was a different story. It was an overbearing and forceful approach, but Rio would have it his way.

That’s...! Celia was clearly faltering.

You’re hesitating, Professor. That’s what it looks like to me, Rio declared bluntly.

B-But it may just be that my thinking process is wrong. I may cause so much trouble for other people if I prioritized my own feelings... Is that really the right thing to do?! Celia said, desperately appealing for her own indecision. In a way, she was confessing her true thoughts about how she didn’t want this marriage to happen in a somewhat roundabout way.

Rio showed the faintest hint of a smile and shook his head. ...I do not know. However, if this marriage really was the right thing to do, then you wouldn’t be making that face, Professor.

Um... Celia’s heart was struck deeply by his words, as her face distorted on the verge of tears.

Professor, please tell me. I will grant your wish; even if it’s a forceful way of doing it, I have acquired enough power to see it through. So, please... don’t give up, Rio said reassuringly.

What’s... with that... Even Celia couldn’t help but laugh bitterly, as though she was astounded by his words. If I said I didn’t want to get married, what would you do? she asked weakly.

...I’d kidnap you and run away from here. I don’t know if the Count Claire house’s position will rise because of it, but at the very least, it won’t cause them to be pursued for responsibility. With the bride being kidnapped before the general public, the cancellation of the wedding would be inevitable. There would be no logical way to put that blame on the Count Claire family. If anything, the responsibility would fall on the shoulders of the security, which would result in Duke Arbor’s family receiving the brunt of the criticism, Rio explained.

You’ve already made this much of a mess of the situation... It seems you really do have the confidence to be able to pull something like that off, Celia said, biting on her lower lip. She didn’t feel any doubt toward Rio’s statement about kidnapping her, but her expression showed faint hesitation. She must have felt guilt at the idea of abandoning her responsibilities to her family and the noble society after all.

Rio seemed to see through those worries of hers. Don’t you think you’ve already fulfilled the bare minimum of your original goal of marrying Charles, Professor? Of course, you’ll be isolating yourself from your family and the noble society if you leave this kingdom, but I will assist you as much as possible to reinstate your noble status and reunite you with your family, if you so wish, he said. Even if Celia were to be kidnapped here, a certain level of social connection had already been formed between the two families, and though it wasn’t impossible, it would definitely be difficult for the Arbor family to abandon the Claire family at this point.

Ahaha... to run away from here and then try to restore everything the way it was... isn’t that a little too hopeful? Or rather, too convenient for me, I wonder... Celia laughed weakly without any confidence.

No. If it’s you, Professor, it’s definitely possible. You’ll be able to put everything back where it should be, Rio stated in a certain tone. It was dazzlingly straightforward, expressing his trust and clear expectations toward Celia.

Celia was so happy she could cry; it was as though her gloomy heart had cleared up in an instant. She certainly felt like anything could be done in this very moment.

...That’s all I had to say. It was a long-winded conversation, but in the end, your life is your own, Professor. Even if I choose to speak up against it, I won’t force you to do anything. So, please — you make the final decision. Although... those aren’t words I should be saying with a knife pointed at you. Rio smiled faintly.

Hey, Rio. Celia said, her heart having already decided.

Yes? Rio replied, awaiting her answer.

Take me away from here. All the way outside of the capital.

With that, the caged bird was set free. Those words were, unmistakably, Celia’s true feelings.

Leave it to me. Rio nodded with determination, happiness flowing from the depths of his heart.

Alfred’s weapon had weight, reach, and more power behind each blow, but Rio challenged him with his sheer number of attacks. Rio swung his daggers to beat Alfred’s blows to the punch, continuing to evade the sharp and heavy slashes. Every time the blades clashed, fireworks sparked and scattered.

Then, after they had exchanged blows for a while, the two parties paused.

...He’s strong. His sword hand is good, and he has no trouble keeping up with my movements that are enhanced by spirit arts. Is there a powerful body enhancement sorcery imbued in that sword? Rio observed Alfred, analyzing his combat abilities. Alfred also observed Rio without letting his guard down, his expression looking somewhat dubious.

Immediately after, the two of them jumped at each other once more. The battle had resumed. From outside Rio’s space, Alfred launched a vertical strike which Rio stopped by raising his daggers upward. The two powers struggled for several creaking moments when Rio pushed out his daggers and thrust Alfred away. Alfred suddenly backstepped away to retreat. Rio used the opportunity to step forward firmly and corner Alfred. Then, swinging the dagger like a dance, he ran freely around Alfred, attacking incessantly.

Alfred only barely managed to block the endless numbers of blows approaching him with his single sword. The knights in the area gulped as they watched over the fierce fight before them. The battle between the two had already reached inhuman levels of strength, leaving no room for third party interference.

“S-Sir Alfred is being pushed back...” The sword flashes of the two parties were already impossible for the human eye to perceive, but the knights beside them could tell that the exchange of offense and defense was beginning to lean in Rio’s favor.

The trigger had been Rio cornering Alfred. When they both put each other within reach, it was obvious that Rio using the flexible and multi-hitting weapon had the advantage.

If Alfred tried to swing widely, the moment Rio evaded him, a fatal opening would inevitably reveal itself. Since Rio had been attacking him persistently for a while now, Alfred was unable to swing his sword at will and was being pressed to handle Rio’s attacks.

That being said, Alfred showed no panic in his eyes, using his long years of battle experience to move his body optimally, calmly waiting for the chance to counterattack.

Then, at one point, Alfred went for the match. While blocking Rio’s swinging daggers, he first leaped backward to widen the distance from Rio. There, Rio stepped forward, immediately trying to close the gap between then. “Hah—” Alfred also stepped forward with force, accelerating as he charged toward Rio. The move backwards had been a feint — his true aim was to create an opening in Rio and land a sharp slashing attack there. However, Rio decelerated as though he had foreseen the counter, coming to a stop just outside of Alfred’s reach.

“?!”

The next moment, Alfred’s sword slashed through thin air, passing just a hair’s breadth away from Rio’s face. Immediately, Rio countered the counter by closing in on Alfred, swinging both his daggers and slashing from both left and right. Alfred’s forward leaning stance created an opening that was by no means small. Rio’s slashing attacks tried to catch hold of Alfred’s body as though they were being sucked in. Alfred reflexively deflected the slash coming from his front left with his sword, then stepped left and slipped away from the slash coming from the right.

However, Rio turned his body, then used that force to strike Alfred with the grip end of his left dagger.

“Kuh...”

Alfred promptly moved his left hand, which was equipped with a gauntlet, and directly stopped Rio’s powerful blow. Though he had avoided a fatal wound, he still felt the impact, a pained expression on his face.

Rio tried a followup attack; he pulled back the dagger in his left hand temporarily and rotated his body once more, swinging his left and right daggers at Alfred.

Alfred leaped backward to avoid Rio’s attack, but his left hand appeared to be injured, as he held his sword with only his right hand. Rio closed in from a low angle, when suddenly, Alfred’s sword started to emit a bright light.

“Haah!” Alfred slashed the glowing sword vertically downward, slamming it against the ground before him. The moment of impact caused a tremor and a shockwave to spread. At the same time, even though it was only afternoon, the surroundings were basked in a bright light. The knights watching nearby couldn’t help but close their eyes. Then, once they had endured the torrent of light and pressing shockwave, they opened their eyes just a bit.

“Wha...” The knights watching the scene were rendered speechless. The stone paving Rio had been running across moments ago had its ground bored deep in a wide area, kicking up a cloud of sand and dust. Before that damaged area stood Alfred, who didn’t see Rio in the area.

...I’ve been underestimated. Did that assailant have no intention of killing me? Alfred thought with a bitter expression. He couldn’t figure out Rio’s intention in pointing the grip end at him when it should have been the blade. However, no matter how much he wondered, his opponent was gone.

There was no resistance... Did he run away? But it didn’t seem like he ran into the alleyway. Where did he go? Alfred thought to himself.

“Sir Alfred!” A single griffin from the patrolling aerial squad descended. The other ground knights that had been standing by also swarmed over.

“I don’t see the bandit in the area. Where is he?!” The knight clearly had the same question as Alfred.

“I don’t know. Though if that attack just now was a direct hit, there wouldn’t be much left of him...” Alfred shook his head with a dark look.

“I-I see...” The knight nodded and gulped, looking at the deeply upturned ground. As far as they could see from the aftermath of the destruction, there was no way Rio could be alive.

Alfred put his doubts aside for the moment and prioritized the search of the alleyways. “All ground units will immediately conduct a search of the alleyways. Squads who come later should take care of the injured. The Aerial Knights will continue to search the skies. He may still be lurking somewhere. Do not let your guard down!”

“Yes, sir!” the knights all replied at once, immediately taking action. However, the knights were never able to locate Celia in the alleyways.

◇　◇　◇

Roughly one hour later, in a hillside area off the road that extended east from the royal capital of Beltrant, Aishia and Celia stood waiting. Celia was holding onto the hem of her skirt and watching the sky nervously, sometimes glancing at Aishia as though remembering her presence.

“Hey, Aishia. Will Rio really be all right?” she asked her for the umpteenth time.

“He’ll be fine.” Aishia nodded calmly. “...He’s coming,” she added, suddenly looking up at the sky toward the capital.

“Huh? How do you know...” Celia looked at Aishia’s face in surprise at her statement. Rio then landed on the ground softly, removing his hood and announcing his return as though he had come back from a leisurely walk.

“I’m back.”

“...Huh?” Celia’s eyes widened in shock.

“I’m sorry for worrying you, Professor. Everything is fine now.”

“Y-Yeah.”

“Thank you, Aishia,” Rio said.

“No, I didn’t really do anything.” Aishia shook her head in her usual way.

“Now, shall we get moving? I’d like to get away from the capital as soon as possible.”

“Okay. But where will we go?”

“I’d like to find some clues about the heroes, too, so I think we’ll head toward the Galarc Kingdom in the east? If you don’t mind, that is,” Rio said, looking at Celia.

“...Huh? Ah, nope. The Galarc Kingdom sounds fine.” Celia nodded readily.

Rio noticed Celia’s awkward behavior and questioned her curiously. “Professor, is something the matter?”

“N-Nothing. It just hasn’t quite hit me yet, so I’m wondering if this is really okay...” Celia replied with an expression that showed her heart wasn’t quite present.

“...Do you want to return to the capital? We can still make it if we leave right now,” he asked hesitantly, observing Celia’s face.

“Huh? N-No, no, that’s not it! Don’t misunderstand! I was just wondering if I was really allowed to be so happy. It just doesn’t quite feel real!” Celia denied Rio’s misunderstanding with panicked gestures.

“Oh?” Rio tilted his head in question.

“Y-Yes... For a moment there, my future was so dark I thought my life was over. But now you’re here and we’ll be able to be together for some time... Just the thought is...” Celia said before she realized she was trying to say something extremely embarrassing and gasped, but it was too late to take back her words at that point.

“O-Obviously I’d be happy about this, don’t you think?” she continued, averting her eyes.

“...Is that so?” Rio smiled happily with a noncommittal response.

“Y-Yeah. That’s why... there might be some things that are on my mind, but there’s no way I’ll regret anything. If anything, I have to think about what to do from here!” Celia stated with motivation.

“Yeah. Let’s talk about things slowly. For the time being, I have no intention of letting you live uncomfortably, so don’t worry about that,” Rio said respectfully.

“Ahaha, really now? But I want to repay you properly, too, Rio. Well, I only have this dress right now, but... I wonder if it’d be worth something if you sell it?” Celia looked at her silver dress and thought contemplatively.

“No, I’d never ask you to sell that. There’s no need for you to worry about money. Just let me look after you for the near future. I am capable of doing that much.”

“But... are you sure?” Celia asked hesitantly.

“Of course. Let me look after you, okay?” Rio replied jokingly.

“...Thank you. Then, I’ll accept your offer and rely on you for a while.” Celia grinned, bowing her head.

Rio nodded acceptingly. “Of course.”

“Same here.” Aishia joined in on the conversation, making Celia nod happily.

“Then, let’s get a move on,” Rio urged.

“...Understood. I’m counting on you for a safe flight, Rio.” Celia held onto the fabric of her dress and stood before Rio nervously.

“Yes. Then, if you’d excuse me...” Rio nodded, lifting Celia awkwardly in the bridal style once more.

“Fufu, let’s talk lots while we’re moving to make up for all the time we couldn’t see each other, okay?” Celia asked with a faint blush, but her smile was radiating brightly with happiness.

“...You seem to be the same species as us humans, so perhaps there isn’t that much difference in our ecosystems?” Liselotte asked, watching Hiroaki’s expression carefully.

“So it seems. That being said, there are plants and animals I don’t know.”

“How fascinating. What kind of place was the world you lived in, hero?” Liselotte asked.

“Well, civilization was a lot more advanced than this world, that’s for sure. The country I’m from is called ‘Japan,’ a relatively advanced country even for my world.”

Liselotte’s eyes narrowed in the faintest at the mention of that name. “Japan, you say? I have one question about that...”

“Hm? What?”

“Why can you understand our language, hero?”

“...Hm? What do you mean?” Hiroaki tilted his head at Liselotte’s question.

“Well, it’s just that I find it strange how the language of another world can be used in this world without any alterations,” Liselotte said, supplementing her question.

“Oh, I see. That’s true...”

This time, Flora was the one to incline her head in confusion. “Umm, what do you mean? Is he not actually communicating in our language?”

“There are a number of theories about the origin of our language, but it is practically impossible for the same language to develop in completely different places. While the common tongue is used widely in the Strahl region nowadays, each area still has its own unique language, not to mention that the hero came from an entirely different world...” Liselotte explained.

Perhaps translation sorcery was cast on him when he was summoned into this world as a hero. I’ve never heard of sorcery like that before, but that’s the only explanation... I’ll have to look into it more when I have a chance. For now, he doesn’t seem to find it strange that several of the Ricca Guild products have Earth names...

“I see... So that’s how it is,” Flora said, understanding in awe.

“Well, it’s not a problem that can be solved simply by dwelling over it. I just found it a little strange, is all. Forgive me for asking such an odd question.” Pressing the issue any further would have been rude and held the possibility of arousing suspicions, so Liselotte chose to back down easily without further pursuing the answer.

“No, I found it strange, too. Though I assumed it was a part of the whole other-world summoning cliché, so I didn’t worry about it at first.” Hiroaki shook his head, unbothered.

“A ‘cliché’...?”

“Ah... Other world journeys are really common in the popular novels I often read. When certain parts of those stories get overused, they’re called ‘tropes’ or ‘clichés.’”

“Is that right? So the hero is educated in both literature and cuisine.” Liselotte placed a hand over her mouth as she smiled elegantly. The gesture would have seemed forced on some people, but it looked more than appropriate for a well-bred girl like her, making her seem very cute.

“Ah, no, not really. But I do believe I’ve read enough of everything to develop an eye for fine quality. I also have a view on all works of art, not only novels.” Hiroaki said in a not at all displeased manner, gloating rather bashfully.

After that, Liselotte continued to cleverly flatter Hiroaki, sometimes directing the conversation to Flora and the others, making the after-meal discussions pleasant. Liselotte was a skilled conversationalist, drawing topic after topic from Hiroaki. They spent nearly an hour like that, until the lone female attendant in the room filled their cups of tea for a third time.

“Oh my, would you look at the time. Talking to the hero was so fun, I was lost in our conversation together,” Liselotte said regretfully, looking at the clock in the room.

Still wanting to talk more, Hiroaki’s face fell. “Ah, is that so? I wanted to talk with Liselotte for a little longer, though...”

“Fufu, thank you very much. However, I heard from Duke Huguenot that there was a matter to be discussed, so we must address that as well.” Liselotte bowed her head apologetically to Hiroaki, before turning to bow to Duke Huguenot too. “Please accept my apologies, Duke Huguenot. I was too immersed in the conversation.”

“No, no, you were merely fulfilling your duty as a hostess and enlivening the atmosphere. Lord Hiroaki and Princess Flora seem to be satisfied, and I was able to hear many interesting stories as well. There is nothing for you to apologize for.” Duke Huguenot smiled brightly and shook his head.

His words were not just flattery; no matter how much of a noble education and upbringing one received, entertaining heroes and foreign royalty would normally be too great a burden for a young noble. However, Liselotte played the role of an entertainer perfectly.

“I am delighted to hear you think so. Thank you very much,” Liselotte said with respectful gratitude. Duke Huguenot was astonished by her masterful conduct.

It is amazing that she’s the same age as Princess Flora. She’s as talented as the rumors say... no, she’s even more talented than the rumors. Roanna — who is a year older — is also quite talented, but she would be at a disadvantage when compared to Liselotte, Huguenot thought to himself, glancing at Roanna, who sat with them as Hiroaki’s assistant.

“Regarding the matter to be discussed... Shameless as it may be, we have a request to make of you.”

Liselotte’s eyes widened in a great deal of surprise. “Oh, is that so? What kind of request might that be?”

Duke Huguenot cut to the chase. “We would like to make a request for your support,” he requested brazenly.

The ability to offer opinions and make requests without cowardice during negotiations was an essential skill for a noble. Being quick to back down because of the mood didn’t always lead to the desired results, and lowering one’s guard carelessly risked being dragged into the opponent’s pace. In a nutshell: being brazen was a noble’s forte.

“Do you mean support for the faction that you’re holding in Marquess Rodan’s territory, Duke Huguenot?” Liselotte asked, showing no particular change of expression. She had nothing to fear, being someone of her position who had faced numerous sly nobles and merchants many times before.

“Yes, that’s right. ...I’d like to take this opportunity to drop all pretenses. Liselotte, how much of our kingdom’s situation are you aware of?” Duke Huguenot asked suddenly, getting to the heart of the matter.

“...If I were to limit my knowledge to confirmed information, then I know the Beltrum army was crushed by the Proxia Empire several months ago. Several strategically located bases and territories were occupied, leading to the reemergence of Duke Arbor’s house after their fall nine years ago. After that, when Duke Arbor pressed His Majesty and Duke Huguenot for responsibility of the defeat, he managed to skillfully seize political power. It was so skillful, it was as though he had arranged everything in advance,” Liselotte explained, speaking eloquently about the facts she had gathered from her information network.

“I see. Considering how much of our country’s situation you have a grasp of, including the unconfirmed information, that is quite impressive indeed.” Duke Huguenot chuckled faintly. Flora and Roanna were both gazing in awe, surprised at how well Liselotte understood their kingdom’s domestic affairs.

“I am merely a minor noble and merchant,” Liselotte said humbly with a cool smile.

“Hahaha, it makes things much easier if you are that aware of the situation. You’re an intelligent individual... I’m sure you’ve already realized the meaning behind why Princess Flora is here with me, no?”

“...That you are backing Princess Flora in order to oppose Duke Arbor, I suppose?”

To put it another way, King Philip III of the Kingdom of Beltrum had entrusted Flora to Duke Huguenot — but Liselotte purposefully chose not to express it like that.

“That’s right. You may be aware already, but we are secretly in the middle of negotiations with the Kingdom of Galarc for its support,” Duke Huguenot confirmed.

“...There’s one thing I’d like to ask you. Would I be correct in assuming that the hero’s presence here means he has also sided with your faction, Duke Huguenot?” Liselotte looked at Hiroaki in question.

“Yeah, that’s right. Geez... I just wanted to quietly live my life without drawing attention to myself, but apparently the situation surrounding me won’t let me do that,” Hiroaki agreed tiredly and shrugged his shoulders.

I guess it’s certain that he’s the strongly self-asserted type, then? Duke Huguenot must have stirred his true nature well to get him to join. There was still a need to observe his personality further, Liselotte analyzed calmly in her head as she smiled.

“I believe our negotiations with the Kingdom of Galarc will conclude in the near future, making us formally allied. At that time, we would like to request your support,” Duke Huguenot stated.

“I am but one young girl. Wouldn’t it be better to seek my father’s cooperation if you wish for political or military assistance?” Liselotte said, avoiding an answer. In reality, she was only the daughter of a duke, so she had no real political or military power outside of her position as Amande’s governor.

Duke Huguenot shook his head bluntly. “No, what we seek is financial support.”

“What do you mean?” Liselotte asked, her eyes fixed on him.

“As you are the president of the Ricca Guild, I am requesting this of you. Would you be willing to invest your company’s valuable resources — funds, goods, and connections — for our sake? You can call this a business negotiation. Of course, you will be duly rewarded,” Duke Huguenot stressed the vital point.

The Ricca Guild was an extremely young organization established by Liselotte, but it was already a high-class trading guild famous in neighboring kingdoms. It continuously produced products that captured not only the hearts of nobles, but commoners too, making its financial influence reach far beyond that of a small kingdom. Such a large trading firm was built up in a single generation, by the still-fifteen-year-old Liselotte.

Consequently, Duke Huguenot was certain that having Liselotte and the Ricca Guild as their allies would be even more beneficial than having the support of the Galarc Kingdom.

“...I understand. In that case, as long as you agree to several of my conditions, I will agree to providing you support,” Liselotte replied after a pause.

Duke Huguenot’s eyes widened faintly. “...That was a rather quick decision. I honestly expected more resistance.”

“Oh? The Ricca Guild isn’t a charity, after all. If it’s a business negotiation with a return for us, then I am willing to invest in it. Please look at these first.” Liselotte smiled cutely, then took out several documents; the female attendant waiting beside her immediately carried them to Duke Huguenot.

“...Oh?” Duke Huguenot ran his eyes over the documents swiftly, before breathing an impressed hum. The document contained the clearly written conditions of the Ricca Guild’s support for the Huguenot faction.

So she saw through our intentions from the start. What truly wonderful talent, Duke Huguenot thought, astonished.

“Hmm. So all that’s left is for us to accept these conditions... Could you allow us some time to carefully consider this?”

“Of course. We can reach a conclusion once you’ve done that. You’re welcome to stay in my estate until you have reached a decision you are satisfied with.”

“That would be greatly appreciated. Then I shall explain the overview of this to Princess Flora and Sir Hiroaki immediately.”

“In that case, a separate room will be prepared for you. Aria?” Liselotte said, addressing the sole attendant in the room.

“Understood. Everyone, please follow me this way.” Aria promptly opened the door of the dining hall and invited Duke Huguenot and the others to step out. Then, after entrusting the party to another attendant waiting outside the room, Aria spoke up again. “She will be the one to guide you there. Please let her know if you need anything.”

Just before he left the room, Duke Huguenot stared at Aria’s face. “...Excuse me for asking, but have we met somewhere before?” he asked curiously.

“...No, I don’t believe so.” Aria shook her head slowly.

“I see. My apologies. Liselotte, I shall see you later. Please excuse us for now,” Duke Huguenot said, seemingly unbothered as he quickly left the room.

Meanwhile, Hiroaki’s eyes were drawn to Aria’s well-proportioned face, but he was urged out of the room by Flora and Roanna behind him.

Thus, once Liselotte and Aria were the only ones left in the dining hall, Liselotte spoke up. “Duke Huguenot seemed to recognize your face. Are you sure you didn’t meet him while you were working in the Beltrum royal castle?” she suddenly asked.

“No, I never actually met him.” Aria shook her head disinterestedly. Liselotte didn’t seem too interested either, as she soon changed the subject.

“I see. Well, that’s fine. More importantly, can I ask how the hero looked to you?”

“...He gave the impression of someone who dislikes being restricted, and he strongly desires to stand out, despite what he was saying. If that wasn’t an act, then I believe he’s simply a young man who craves the limelight after obtaining undeserving power so suddenly.”

“Harsh. But accurate,” Liselotte agreed with a wry smile. If he really didn’t want to stand out, then he didn’t have to be the hero. The fact he was sticking his neck into the kingdom’s affairs was proof of that contradiction. Otherwise, there had to be a reason why he had to act as the hero.

He may be easy to handle now, but those types of people are more bothersome to handle when aggravated. Duke Huguenot was probably aware of that, thought Liselotte.

Epilogue: The Cerulean Lady

That night, in a room of the guest building inside the Beltrum royal castle premises, the noble daughter of the Galarc Kingdom’s great lord Duke Cretia, Liselotte, was eating her dinner alone.

“The business talk that was planned has been placed on hold, so it looks like our return to Amande will be delayed,” Liselotte muttered listlessly.

She had been invited to Celia’s wedding as a noble and great merchant of the Kingdom of Galarc, but with the ceremony suspended, she had been forced to stay in the guest house until now. Because the Kingdom of Beltrum was in an uproar over Celia’s kidnapping, she had been forbidden to step outside under the name of protection.

“We’ll be able to leave the guest house in a few days, but with the situation being what it is, please forget your work and allow yourself some time to relax,” Aria, the attendant standing next to Liselotte, said.

“You say that, but there isn’t really anything to do. The current collapse of the Arbor house is fairly interesting to the Galarc Kingdom... Or rather, something to be thankful for. You think the same, no?” Liselotte said with a giggle.

“It is indeed exhilarating to witness. Although, I am concerned for Celia.” Even the usually emotionless Aria showed some conflict in her tone.

“...Who do you think the culprit is?” Liselotte suddenly asked.

“Considering the options, I believe it is very likely to be one of the opposing forces to Duke Arbor’s faction.”

“If that’s the case, then I don’t think she’ll be treated badly, since there’s still value in using her... But the number of people who could make such a mess is fairly limited, no? Would you be able to pull something like this off?”

“It may be possible for me if I had a powerful magic sword imbued with physical ability enhancement like an ancient artifact... But honestly, it would be a struggle. There would be a high chance of failure,” Aria explained.

“Even someone as skilled as you would hesitate at the risk?”

“If I were to plan an ambush, it should be easy to gain the advantage and reach the carriage. The problem is how to take Celia and run away successfully. It would be one thing if the opponent only had ground units, but when the pursuers can cover the skies, it gets quite troublesome,” Aria said, giving an orderly answer to the question.

“I see.” Liselotte nodded, sighing in thought.

All of the kingdoms have been acting so shady lately. I don’t know if its related to the incident this time, but the Proxia Empire in particular cannot be ignored. It feels like they’re planning something big. While Liselotte wondered such things, Aria stood silently beside her, waiting for her master to speak up.

“Well, like you said... let’s enjoy this short break and relax. Tell those who accompanied us here that they should rest once in a while, too. Things will get busy once we get back to Amande,” Liselotte said, giving a small shrug of her shoulders.

“Understood.” Aria nodded respectfully.

The Galarc Kingdom will have to work harder. The hero that was summoned in the castle, Satsuki Sumeragi, is going to be announced soon, too, Liselotte thought as she took another sip of her slightly cooled soup.